

Jaewon Lee

ROBOTICS · MULTI-ROBOT · SLAM

25, Galmaejungang-ro, Guri-si, Gyeonggi-do, 11902, Rep. of KOREA

 $\ \square$ (+82) 10-9114-2756 | $\ \blacksquare$ ashcircle@kw.ac.kr | $\ \blacksquare$ lee-jaewon.github.io | $\ \boxdot$ Lee-JaeWon

"Passion is the genesis of genius."

Summary.

This is Jaewon Lee, who wants to be a Robotics researcher and engineer. I am interested in Robotics, SLAM, Multi-Robot System. I think Robotics can help the development of the world a lot. I want to study a lot and approach the world.

Research Interests

SLAM Multi-Robot, Descriptor

Novel View Synthesis 3D Scene Representation, Sensor-Fused Representation

Education

Yonsei University @CILAB

Seoul, S.Korea

COMBINED M.S. & Ph.D. IN ELECTRICAL AND ELECTRONIC ENGINEERING (ADVISOR: PROF. EUNTAI KIM)

Mar. 2024(Expected) -

• Research on Robotics

KwangWoon University

Seoul, S.Kore

B.S. IN SCHOOL OF ROBOTICS

Mar. 2020 - Feb. 2024

- GPA: 4.13/4.50, Major GPA: 4.29/4.50
- Club: BARAM Robotics (Robotics Academic Group) [2022 Vice President], Mar.2020-Feb.2024

Work Experience_

Yonsei University @CILAB

Seoul, S.Kored

Undergraduate LAB Intern (Advisor: PROF. Euntai Kim)

Jul. 2023 - Present

- I Participated in ICCV 2023 SLAM Challenge
- I studied 3D Scene Representation

ROBOMATION

Seoul, S.Korea

Jun. 2022 - Aug. 2022

R&D Intern

I developed an automation system for soccer games using multi-robot.

I developed an automation system for soccer games using multi-robot.
 I developed multi-robot coordination and pose system using Aruco Marker.

KwangWoon University @Robotics A.I. LAB.

2022.10 Dean's list, for Academic Excellence

Seoul, S.Kored

Undergraduate LAB Intern (Advisor: PROF. Junghyun Oh)

Jan. 2022 - Jun. 2022

- I studied visual SLAM and visual odometry
- I studied Multi-Robot system and implemented Multi-Robot exploration

Honors & Awards

AWARDS

2023.12	2023 Hanium ICT Mentoring Competition, Silver Award	Ministry of Science and ICT, IITP, FKii
2023.10	ICCV 2023 SLAM Challenge, Fourth place in LiDAR-Inertial Track - Taeyoung Kim, Jaewon Lee, Beomsoo Kim, Euntai Kim	ICCV 2023
2023.06	Undergraduate Paper Award, Paper - Autonomous multi robot parking system	ICROS 2023

HONORS

2022.10 Full Tuition Scholarship, for the first place in last semester

Kwangwoon Univ.

Publication

DOMESTIC CONFERENCE

"Autonomous Multi Robot Parking System",

Jaewon Lee, Hyosuk Joo, Chung-gil Ahn, Hyedo Kim, Junghyun Oh - [Paper]

ICROS 2023

Skills_

Programming C++/C, Python, MATLAB **DevOps** ROS/ROS2, Docker, Git

Framework PyTorch, Tensorflow, Keras, Unity

Extracurricular Activity

Technical Blog - lee-jaewon.github.io

Personal Tech Blog

WRITER

Jul. 2021 - Present

- I have been writing posts about the paper review, development, the study of Interests.
- · To study through writing and sharing.
- The blog is available at [here].

Autonomous Multi Robot Parking System

Kwangwoon Univ.

CAPSTONE DESIGN

Jan.2023 - Jun.2023

- · Implement a multi-robot system and implement various technologies necessary for mobile robots.
- The source code for the project is available at [my GitHub repository].

2022 Open Source Contribution Academy

Ministry of Science and ICT, NIPA

MENTEE

Jul. 2022 - Oct. 2022

• I contributed to translating PyTorch Hub English documents into Korean at the PyTorch Korean User's Group.

Multi Robot Collision Avoidance with Velocity Obstacle

BARAM Robotic

PERSONAL PROJECT

Sep.2022 - Nov.2022

- $\bullet \ \ {\sf I} \ {\sf implemented} \ {\sf collision} \ {\sf avoidance} \ {\sf with} \ {\sf Velocity} \ {\sf Obstacle} \ {\sf using} \ {\sf multi-robot}.$
- The source code for the project is available at [my GitHub repository].

Autonomous Driving Simulation with Reinforcement Learning

BARAM Robotic

PERSONAL PROJECT

Sep.2021 - Nov.2021

- I implemented an Autonomous-driving system through DQN algorithm for the high-way situation.
- I implemented a simulator with Unity. And I managed the reward using Laser Sensor.
- The source code for the project is available at [my GitHub repository].

Frontier Based Multi-Robot Exploration

BARAM Robotic

PERSONAL PROJECT

Mar.2022 - Jun.2022

- I implemented ROS-based multi-robot frontier exploration.
- I implemented a multi-robot SLAM system using open sources.
- The source code for the project is available at [my GitHub repository].

House Interior Classifier and Automatic Recommendation

022 Deen Learning Lecture

DEEP-LEARNING PROJECT

Mar.2022 - Jun.2022

- I implemented House Interior Classifier using Inception-Resnet-V2 in Keras.
- · I implemented a system that can automatically search on the actual shopping site with the classified result.
- The source code for the project is available at [my GitHub repository].